[
    {"question":"鰯",
     "answer":"いわし"},
    {"question":"鮎",
     "answer":"あゆ"},
    {"question":"鯛",
     "answer":"たい"},
    {"question":"鰤",
     "answer":"ぶり"},
    {"question":"鯰",
     "answer":"なまず"},
    {"question":"鯉",
     "answer":"こい"},
    {"question":"秋刀魚",
     "answer":"さんま"},
    {"question":"鱸",
     "answer":"すずき"},
    {"question":"鱚",
     "answer":"きす"},
    {"question":"鱓",
     "answer":"うつぼ"},
    {"question":"鰹",
     "answer":"かつお"},
    {"question":"鱈",
     "answer":"たら"},
    {"question":"穴子",
     "answer":"あなご"},
    {"question":"狆穴子",
     "answer":"ちんあなご"},
    {"question":"鮭",
     "answer":"さけ"},
    {"question":"鰻",
     "answer":"うなぎ"},
    {"question":"河豚",
     "answer":"ふぐ"},
    {"question":"鯒",
     "answer":"こち"},
    {"question":"鱧",
     "answer":"はも"},
    {"question":"鮟鱇",
     "answer":"あんこう"},
    {"question":"鰆",
     "answer":"さわら"},
    {"question":"虎魚",
     "answer":"おこぜ"},
    {"question":"魚虎",
     "answer":"はりせんぼん"},
    {"question":"鮪",
     "answer":"まぐろ"},
    {"question":"目撥鮪",
     "answer":"めばちまぐろ"},
    {"question":"旗魚",
     "answer":"かじき"},
    {"question":"小鰭",
     "answer":"こはだ"},
    {"question":"鯵",
     "answer":"あじ"},
    {"question":"魬",
     "answer":"はまち"},
    {"question":"鮴",
     "answer":"めばる"},
    {"question":"鮋",
     "answer":"かさご"},
    {"question":"鯡",
     "answer":"にしん"},
    {"question":"天魚",
     "answer":"あまご"},
    {"question":"山女魚",
     "answer":"やまめ"},
    {"question":"鮒",
     "answer":"ふな"},
    {"question":"鶏魚",
     "answer":"いさき"},
    {"question":"鮍",
     "answer":"かわはぎ"},
    {"question":"間八",
     "answer":"かんぱち"},
    {"question":"鮃",
     "answer":"ひらめ"},
    {"question":"鯖",
     "answer":"さば"},
    {"question":"鱵",
     "answer":"さより"},
    {"question":"垢穢",
     "answer":"くえ"},
    {"question":"鱏",
     "answer":"えい"},
    {"question":"翻車魚",
     "answer":"まんぼう"},
    {"question":"鱰",
     "answer":"しいら"},
    {"question":"隈魚",
     "answer":"くまのみ"},
    {"question":"鰌",
     "answer":"どじょう"},
    {"question":"鮱",
     "answer":"おおぼら"},
    {"question":"柳葉魚",
     "answer":"ししゃも"},
    {"question":"𩹉",
     "answer":"とびうお"},
    {"question":"魛",
     "answer":"たちうお"},
    {"question":"鮗",
     "answer":"このしろ"},
    {"question":"𩸽",
     "answer":"ほっけ"},
    {"question":"鱒",
     "answer":"ます"},
    {"question":"鰙",
     "answer":"わかさぎ"},
    {"question":"鱂",
     "answer":"めだか"},
    {"question":"白子(×しらこ)",
     "answer":"しらす"},
    {"question":"竹麦魚",
     "answer":"ほうぼう"},
    {"question":"鰈",
     "answer":"かれい"},
    {"question":"介党鱈",
     "answer":"すけとうだら"},
    {"question":"鰰",
     "answer":"はたはた"},
    {"question":"赤鯥",
     "answer":"あかむつ"},
    {"question":"薔薇鯥",
     "answer":"ばらむつ"},
    {"question":"鯥五郎",
     "answer":"むつごろう"},
    {"question":"老翁(×ろうおう)",
     "answer":"おじさん"},
    {"question":"鮫",
     "answer":"さめ"},
    {"question":"蝶鮫",
     "answer":"ちょうざめ"},
    {"question":"撞木鮫",
     "answer":"しゅもくざめ"},
    {"question":"葦切鮫",
     "answer":"よしきりざめ"},
    {"question":"甚兵衛鮫",
     "answer":"じんべえざめ"},
    {"question":"鋸刺鮭",
     "answer":"ぴらにあ"}
]